https://www.storkgifts.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

My Account
Cart(0)
enjoy free shipping on all orders!
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
Security Policy
Storkgifts.com uses technology called Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to encrypt any personal information you transmit to us online. The information is encrypted on your computer and decoded after it reaches Storkgifts.com's secure server. This information cannot be decrypted during transit. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, you cannot be held liable for more than $50.00 of unauthorized charges on your card. Shopping online at Storkgifts.com is statistically safer than using your credit card at a restaurant or department store. Technical experts point out that online purchases without human intervention are far safer than traditional credit card transactions because the information is immediately encrypted into a scrambled message that can only be decrypted by an authorized computer. If you are still nervous about ordering online, once you have selected your products we encourage you to call our Customer Service department at 866-786-7544 and we will be happy to place your order for you over the phone.
What Information We Collect and Why
We collect personal information primarily so that we may process your order, but also so that we may personalize your purchases and make your shopping experience as unique as possible. In addition to personal information collected for purposes of processing your order, we may ask for the following information:
Billing and Shipping Information
During the checkout process, we ask for certain personal information - name, address, e-mail, telephone number and credit card information - all of which are necessary for us to process your order and ship it to you. Basic personal information such as name, address and telephone number, but not credit card numbers, may be transmitted to contracted third parties (UPS, FedEx, etc.) solely for the purpose of shipping your order. As described above, ordering with Storkgifts.com is safe and secure because we use Secure Socket Layer Technology which encrypts the information you send to us. This information cannot be decrypted during transmission and is decoded on Storkgifts.com's secure server, which cannot be accessed by 3rd parties. Storkgifts.com may also use this information to send you our printed catalog or other announcements via postal mail.
Personalization Information
In order to hand-personalize each product, Storkgifts.com requires that you submit certain private information to us for most items. This may consist of your child's name(s) or age(s), birthdate(s), etc. This information is used only to personalize your purchases, and is held strictly confidential.
E-mail Addresses
During the checkout process, we collect your e-mail address. Your e-mail address is used in the order process. We will occasionally send offers of special deals and coupons on our products. This information is never sold or rented to third parties. At any time, you may modify your information by sending an e-mail to info@storkgifts.com.
Web Statistics
We use a 3rd party web statistics provider Google. This is to track and understand visitor behavior in order to provide a better customer experience. This information is never tied to any specific customer and is anonymous. Google analytics privacy policy can be found at googleanalytics.com.
Cookies
Storkgifts.com uses a feature of your Internet web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. Storkgifts.com creates and then uses these cookie files to track your cart contents and to recognize you when you return to Storkgifts.com's site. This saves you from having to re-input your billing and shipping information the next time you shop with us. Cookies cannot be used by Storkgifts.com to retrieve any personal information about you unless you have previously purchased from Storkgifts.com. Storkgifts.com does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you. In some instances, your browser may have been set to not accept cookies. If so, you will see a message when the Storkgifts.com web site tries to access any cookies. By default, most all browsers are setup to accept cookies when first installed. If your is not, you can change your cookie settings usually in the "Security Options" or "Preferences" section of your browser (or something similar).
Gift Price Range
Select your Range
less than $10
$10 to $20
$20 to $30
$30 to $40
$40 to $50
$50 to $60
$60 to $70
$70 to $80
$80 to $90
$90 and above
Shop By Category
Personalized Step StoolsPersonalized Piggy BanksPersonalized Name PuzzlesPersonalized Jewelry BoxesPersonalized BooksPersonalized Room DecorBaby and Children's FurniturePersonalized PillowcasesClothing and AccessoriesPersonalized Baby BlanketsImaginative PlayPersonalized FramesEducational ItemsReplacement LettersGift Certificates
We Accept
BoysGirlsNew BabySiblingsTweensDesign CollectionsNew ProductsShop by Category
Copyright 2020 Storkgifts. Inc. All Rights Reserved.
